teamblind.com 2019-04-05

# Blind

Welcome to Teamblind, Inc. ("Teamblind" "we," "us" or "our"). Our Privacy Policy explains how we and some of the companies we work with collect, use, share and protect information in relation to our mobile services, and any other services we provide (collectively, the “Services” or “Blind”).

By using our Service you understand and agree that we are providing a platform for you to post text, graphics, photos or other materials (collectively referred to as "Content"), to the Service and to share Content publicly. This means that other users may search for, see, use, or share any of your Content that you make publicly available through the Service, consistent with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.

1\. Information We collect

1.1. Information you provide us directly

1.1.1. Your username, password and valid e-mail address you use for your company when you register for a Teamblind account. We do not require that you provide us with your user profile (e.g., first and last name, picture, phone number).

1.1.2. Content (e.g., comments and other materials) that you post to the Service.

1.2. Analytics information. We use third-party analytics tools to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service. These tools collect information sent by your device or our Service, including the web pages you visit, add-ons, and other information that assists us in improving the Service. We collect and use this analytics information with analytics information from other users so that it cannot reasonably be used to identify any particular individual User.

1.3. Cookies and similar technologies: Like many websites, we may use cookies and similar technologies but only for limited purposes such as, to help authenticate your access to message boards and prevent unauthorized parties from accessing your account, and to store an identifier or other information on your device.

2\. How We Store Your Information

2.1. Your account information (e.g., user name, password, and email address) will be encrypted as soon as you register for the Service, and we store and process such encrypted information in the United States or any other country in which we maintain facilities.

2.1.1. We will use commercially reasonable safeguards and take reasonable steps to keep the information encrypted at all times, so that the information will not be decrypted and accessible. 

2.2. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to the service at all times as we are not able to decrypt and access your encrypted account information.

3\. How We Use and Share Your Information

In addition to some of the specific uses of information we describe in this Privacy Policy, we may use information that we receive: 

• to provide, improve, test, and monitor the effectiveness of our Service; 

• to develop and test new products and features; 

• to diagnose or fix technology problems; 

• for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, and research 

• to display, share, or publish any Content you have submitted for the benefit of our Service; 

• to create statistical data and poll results that does not identify you individually and that we can commercialize. 

• to provide relevant advertising which may mean that we share non-personally identifiable information to third-party advertisers 

We may use the information you submit or post on any inter-company message board except your personal contents provided on private-company message board or sent via direct message. Any information you submit or post on private-company message board or via direct message shall be private or quarantined.

We will not rent or sell your information to third parties outside Teamblind without your consent, except as noted in this Policy. 

• In the event of a change of control. If we sell or otherwise transfer part or the whole of Teamblind or our assets to another organization (e.g., in the course of a transaction like a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, liquidation), your information such as username and encrypted email address, Content and any other information collected through the Service may be among the items sold or transferred. You will continue to own your User Content. The buyer or transferee will have to honor the commitments we have made in this Privacy Policy. We will notify you of such event before it comes into effect, and provide you with detail procedures as to how you can opt out from such information transfer. 

• Responding to legal requests and preventing harm. As indicated in Section 2.1 above, all the information you provide us, including your account information, will be stored in encrypted format, and we will not be able to identify who provided the information once such information is stored in our system. We may access, preserve and share part of such information in response to a legal request if we have a good faith belief that the law requires us to do so. However, the information that Teamblind can provide does not include any information that can be used to identify a specific individual.

4\. Children’s Privacy

Teamblind does not knowingly collect or solicit any information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register for the Service. The Service and its content are not directed at children under the age of 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us.

5\. Change to Our Privacy Policy

Teamblind may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please review it periodically. We may provide you additional forms of notice of modifications or updates as appropriate under the circumstances. Your continued use of Teamblind or the Service after any modification to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such modification.

Effective: September 18, 2014

Last Updated: November 25, 2016
